const quizzes = [
  {
    id: "1",
    title: "Level One",
    questions: [
      {
        prompt: "What is 1 + 3?",
        optionA: "24",
        optionB: "21",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "D",
      },
      {
        prompt: "What is 2 + 3?",
        optionA: "24",
        optionB: "5",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "B",
      },
      {
        prompt: "What is 0 + 3?",
        optionA: "3",
        optionB: "21",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "A",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    title: "Level Two",
    questions: [
      {
        prompt: "What is 1 + 3?",
        optionA: "24",
        optionB: "21",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "D",
      },
      {
        prompt: "What is 2 + 3?",
        optionA: "24",
        optionB: "5",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "B",
      },
      {
        prompt: "What is 0 + 3?",
        optionA: "3",
        optionB: "21",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "A",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    title: "Level Three",
    questions: [
      {
        prompt: "What is 1 + 3?",
        optionA: "24",
        optionB: "21",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "D",
      },
      {
        prompt: "What is 2 + 3?",
        optionA: "24",
        optionB: "5",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "B",
      },
      {
        prompt: "What is 0 + 3?",
        optionA: "3",
        optionB: "21",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "A",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    title: "Level Four",
    questions: [
      {
        prompt: "What is 1 + 3?",
        optionA: "24",
        optionB: "21",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "D",
      },
      {
        prompt: "What is 2 + 3?",
        optionA: "24",
        optionB: "5",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "B",
      },
      {
        prompt: "What is 0 + 3?",
        optionA: "3",
        optionB: "21",
        optionC: "2",
        optionD: "4",
        answer: "A",
      },
    ],
  },
];

export default quizzes;
